Every time the rain no longer
falls, and I see the sky?
I think back to when I was a child.
Who could only cry?
Blindly chasing after him.
I fell far behind my only thought.
One day I will be stronger!
Bridery and gratitude.
Fading with the wind.
Am I stronger now than I was before?
Or as weak as back then?
I don't know for sure.
But until I do, my voyage will not end.
No matter what's next, I'm
walking straight ahead!
So let's go, there's nothing
that can stop us now!
Though times are on our side,
we'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall, but we'll
always keep on standing.
There's no way anything will take
what I hold dear away from me.
The voices inside me push
me to keep surviving.
I'll go on, I'll get through,
no matter what I gotta do!
The fiercest of the ball can pour upon me.
I don't care why in the
world would I turn back?
So let's go!
There's nothing that can stop us now!
Though times love on our side?
We'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall.
But we'll always keep on standing.
There's no way anything?
Will take what I hold dear away from me.
I know the future's there for us to see.
But we were so close!
Oh
He's why!
I'm sorry.
They got Firefist! He's dead!
Strawboy, no!
The poor kid's shutting down!
He's got to get killed!
Akainu!
I won't miss twice!
There's no one to save you!
It's over, Straw Hat!
I've seen enough death for today.
Back off!
Wake up, Luffy!
We have to run!
Move or you're next!
Listen, we cannot give in to despair!
Go carry Straw Hat!
If you won't run, hurry!
We may have lost Ace today, but
he'll live on through Luffy!
You're right, boss!
If Ace can't protect him, then as
his family, we have to step up!
Ace is our brother!
Fight like your pride's
on the line in his honor!
Pull it together for your
brother's sake, Loopy!
When I hold an execution, I make
damn sure to finish the job!
You can't run from me!
Look behind you!
Oh, my God.
Damn, he's mad as hell!
Come on, we gotta get out of here!
Ugh!
Oh, no!
What are you doing for me?
Oh, my God.
Oh!
He's too strong!
HQ's done for!
Son of a...
Whitefeel!
Admiral Sakazuki!
Come on!
Come on, help!
I...
I think it's stopped.
Damn it, why?
The plaza split in half.
We can't reach the pirates.
Awaiting orders.
He's stuck over there.
We can't even fight!
But why?
I thought the man was on his last leg.
Where is all this power coming from?
Want more?
I am your enemy.
And I alone.
So if you have a resolve to face me, come!
Retreat!
Get back to the ship! Hell no!
All we can do is honor his wishes.
As his sons, we should be grateful
and hold our heads up high!
Save your tears for later!
Let's move! I'm done!
I can't! Stand up!
If a ship can sail, bring it to
the bayhead and line him off!
We can still shoot you, dammit!
I'm wasting time!
Salome, take me to Luffy.
I fear for his safety.
Sorry for disobeying orders, but someone's
got to watch this to the end, Pops.
AHHHHH! GAH!
GAH!
GAH! GAH!
Hey, look!
What the hell is that?
It's huge!
Whatever it is it can't be good.
Oops they found me
there's someone else too.
There's a whole group of people up
on the scaffold you fellas ain't
very observant are you blackbeard it
seems you've made some new friends.
I thought they were locked
up and impelled down.
Teach.
They were supposed to
be erased from history.
After the crimes they committed,?
even death was too great a mercy!
He's the largest living
creature in the world!
The great battleship, San Juan Wolf!
Wow, they even know my name.
Well, I'll be...
The corrupt king, Avalopizarro!
Now I'm back!
Now you die!
Heavy drinker, Vasco, shut!
I'm gonna go ahead and
kill them all, okay?
Crescent Moon Hunter!
Katarina Devon!
Maroon!
You boys want this?
Try me.
And that's the old jail
manager from Impel Down!
Shiryu of the Reign!
They've joined the Blackbeard Pirates!
See?
Hey there, pups.
I'm glad I could make it to your funeral.
You miss me, you fat bastard.
Shit of you.
What's going on?
What happened at Impelled Down I have a
hunch that Magellan didn't release you?
How did you make it to Marine Ford?
Well old friend maybe
you ought to worry less
about how we got here
and worry more about what
You're going to do now
that we are if you want
to find out more check
out Impelled Down later?
That'll give you an idea.
By the way, I'm switching sides
in case you couldn't tell.
Figured you might want to know that.
Lead Admiral Sengoku!
I'm sorry I wasn't able
to inform you sooner, sir.
We received a report that the Gates
of Justice opened a second time,
and an unidentified ship
was able to pass through!
So that's how they made it.
But the control room is
under Navy operation.
Nothing else unusual was reported either.
So how could you slip past us undetected?
That's where I'll take credit.
Allow me to explain.
Rapscallions that we are,
we crashed the party at Impel Down
and picked up your old friend.
Then I thought I'd have a spot of fun and
hypnotize the Navy soldiers
in the control room.
I made them open the Gates of Justice
for any Navy ship that approached.
Incidentally, that seems to have helped
a few other rogues get through as well.
And since I was considered a navy
ally, I got through just fine.
If it weren't for my title, I couldn't
have made it inside the prison either.
Long story short, being a warlord
made this little operation a cinch.
But now I'm through with you.
You used us just to bolster
the ranks of your crew?
The old soldier finally figured it out!
My plan is almost complete now!
You'll see soon enough!
Let's finish this, you damn traitor!
Dash!
Captain! Incoming!
Now that was close.
Good to see our reflexes
are still in order.
So much for old times.
Guess I can't blame you.
Of all the pirates who have
called the Moby Dick their home,
you're the only one I refuse
to call my son. Teach.
There is only one rule I have on
my ship, and you dared to break it.
You betrayed our trust by
killing your fellow mate.
It's time to put an end to this.
You'll pay for 4th Division Commander
Thatcher's death with your life.
Mark my words, he will be avenged.
Pops, what are you doing?
Marco!
Let me help you!
Listen, you stay out of this one, boy.
But you're hurt!
Did you hear me?
Let's get this over with right now. See?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
What do you think I'm here for?
Uh oh!
What's that black stuff
coming out of his body?
Is that... smoke?
Enjoy this black hole.
See?
This Devil Fruit power is
exactly why I killed Fish.
I knew I had to have it.
Dark, dark fruit is real tasty.
Why don't you give it a try?
Why?
Don't worry, there's plenty to go around.
You know there's a pattern.
First Thatch kicks the bucket,
and now Ace has followed suit.
All your top underlings seem
to be dropping like flies,
and you're too old to do
a damn thing about it.
Good thing I'm no longer under your thumb.
If I hadn't have gotten out when I did,
who knows where I would have ended up.
And I'll have you know,
I spared him at Bonnaroo Island
when I could have killed him.
I will not stand for this!
Easy now, don't even bother!
Your power won't work against
me, no Devil Fruit power will!
This darkness of mine is
pretty handy, ain't it?
I can nullify your fancy little tricks
just like I did with good old Ace.
In other words, no more
earthquakes, not against me!
You're arrogant, a fool.
You were never fit to be in my crew.
Hey, hold on!
Pops, please don't!
I'm your son, Pops! Stop it!
You wouldn't gun your own son!
He did it!
There you go, Pops!
Hey, look!
He's still alive!
Get away from me, you monster!
I said get away from me!
Damn it!
Will you just die already?
No, don't do it!
Finish him off! Hurry!
Come on, Pops!
Please don't die!
What do you mean, Roger?
You're going to die?
Yeah, I could just feel it.
Do you want to know how to get to Raptal?
I could tell you, if you'd like.
Don't bother.
I've got no interest in that place.
Those world government clowns
don't know what they're doing.
Do you know what they've
been calling me these days?
They call me Gold Roger.
So what?
I thought that was your name.
Do you want to go by something else now?
No, no, you don't get it.
My real name is Gold D. Roger.
Every now and then I come across
someone with a D in their name.
Like my crew member, Marshal D. Teach.
So, what does the D stand for?
That?
You wanna know, huh?
Fine, fine.
I can tell you.
It's a story from way back when.
Hey I'm out of bullets someone give
me another gun it's not you teach
No way he's still alive
The man that Gold D Roger was waiting
for it's not you teach not a damn chance
Just as there are people out there who
inherited Roger's will, soon enough,
someone will carry on
in Ace's name as well.
You may try to destroy their spirit, but
you will never extinguish their flame.
So it has been, and so it shall continue
to be from now till the very end of time.
And one day in the future,
when we're all dead and gone?
Someone will arise
carrying generations upon
generations of our
history on his shoulders!
And he'll throw down the gauntlet
in front of the entire world.
Sengoku, you and the
government know what's coming!
A war that will embroil
the seas far and wide.
That's why you're so afraid.
Though nothing you do will stop it,
I've no interest in it myself,
but someday?
That treasure will turn this world upside
down, you know what I'm talking about,
and I'm sure that someone will find
it whether you like it or not that?
That day will come soon.
The One Piece!
The One Piece is real!
You bastard!
Now that was a touching conclusion
Forgive me, my sons
I raised a fool, and I
couldn't take responsibility
But you boys gave me everything I
could have ever wanted out of life
I've reached the end of my voyage
you don't even care about
treasure why else would you be
in the game well fine what are
you looking for then hey you
listening new gates there's
only one thing i need and i've
wanted it since i was a kid huh
i thought so spill the beans
I want a family a family that's
a joke right I am deeply grateful
goodbye my sons
he's dead i can't believe that
bastard he just died on his feet
And so, Whitebeard passes.
Even after death, his
body remains upright.
The haunting image of his battered
body, which mowed down his enemies,
was a sight to behold.
The final tally of sword wounds he received
in this battle was no less than 267.
The number of gunshot wounds, 152.
He was struck by cannonballs 46 times.
And yet,
if you were to look upon the proud back of
this great man You would see that in this
battle And indeed his
entire life as a pirate
It remained unmarred
by any sign of retreat.